{
    "id": "2290b7d5404f4b7c9650f8af8a02fde4",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The purse was …………………………. to the owner.",
            "description": "To hand something over to somebody is to give it to them.",
            "answers": [
                "handed over",
                "handed in",
                "handed out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… at the next station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got out",
                "got off",
                "got over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My friend is going to ……………………….. a new firm.",
            "description": "To set up is to establish.",
            "answers": [
                "set out",
                "set up",
                "set on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rebellion was ………………………….. by the army.",
            "description": "To put something down is to suppress it.",
            "answers": [
                "put out",
                "put down",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest has not ………………………….. yet although it is time for the meeting to start.",
            "description": "To turn up is to arrive. ",
            "answers": [
                "turned out",
                "turned up",
                "turned in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………………. that he was a spy.",
            "description": "Turn out can mean to be discovered to be something ",
            "answers": [
                "turned up",
                "turned out",
                "turned in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The miser …………………………. a cry when he learnt that his money was lost.",
            "description": "Let out can mean make a noise.",
            "answers": [
                "let up",
                "let in",
                "let out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How did he …………………………….. so much wealth?",
            "description": "To come by wealth is to acquire it.",
            "answers": [
                "come on",
                "come by",
                "come into"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t …………………………. what he was saying.",
            "description": "To make out is to understand.",
            "answers": [
                "make out",
                "make up",
                "make off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor advised him to ………………………………… smoking.",
            "description": "To give up smoking is to quit smoking.",
            "answers": [
                "give off",
                "give up",
                "give in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His application was …………………………..",
            "description": "To turn down application is to reject it.",
            "answers": [
                "turned out",
                "turned in",
                "turned down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not ……………………………. to temptations.",
            "description": "Give way can mean surrender. ",
            "answers": [
                "give way",
                "give up",
                "give off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}